<resources>
    <string name="app_name">DG Playground</string>
    <string name="add_row">Add Row</string>
    <string name="run">Run</string>
    <string name="sort">Sort</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">navigation_drawer_open</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">navigation_drawer_close</string>
    <string name="about">About</string>
    <string name="illegal_values">Illegal values!</string>
    <string name="about_message">
        This program processes a list of vertexes given in the form of a source and destination node numbers,
        starting at 0, describing a directed graph.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;
        The output is a list of all elementary circuits of the graph given.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;
        &lt;b&gt;The algorithm is based on:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br/&gt;
        Johnson, D.B. (1975) &lt;i&gt;Finding All the Elementary Circuits of a Directed Graph.&lt;/i&gt; SIAM Journal on Computing, 4, 77-84.&lt;br/&gt;
        &lt;a href="http://dx.doi.org/10.1137/0204007"&gt;http://dx.doi.org/10.1137/0204007&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;
        &lt;b&gt;Implementation was taken from:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br/&gt;
        &lt;a href="https://github.com/josch/cycles_johnson_meyer"&gt;https://github.com/josch/cycles_johnson_meyer&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;
        &lt;b&gt;And forked as:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br/&gt;
        &lt;a href="https://github.com/udif/cycles_johnson_meyer/tree/dev"&gt;https://github.com/udif/cycles_johnson_meyer/tree/dev&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;
        &lt;b&gt;Program Icon was taken from:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br/&gt;
        &lt;a href="https://www.flaticon.com/free-icons/graph" title="graph icons"&gt;Graph icons created by SBTS2018 - Flaticon&lt;/a&gt;
    </string>
    <string name="about_implementation">Graph library license</string>
    <string name="implementation_license">
    (BSD-2 license)&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;

    Copyright © 2012, Frank Meyer&lt;br/&gt;
    All rights reserved.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;

    Redistribution and use in source and binary forms, with or without modification, are permitted provided that the following conditions are met:&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;

    Redistributions of source code must retain the above copyright notice, this list of conditions and the following disclaimer.&lt;br/&gt;
    Redistributions in binary form must reproduce the above copyright notice, this list of conditions and the following disclaimer in the documentation and/or other materials provided with the distribution.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;

    THIS SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED BY THE COPYRIGHT HOLDERS AND CONTRIBUTORS "AS IS" AND ANY EXPRESS OR IMPLIED WARRANTIES, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, THE IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY AND FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE ARE DISCLAIMED. IN NO EVENT SHALL THE COPYRIGHT HOLDER OR CONTRIBUTORS BE LIABLE FOR ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL, SPECIAL, EXEMPLARY, OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES (INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, PROCUREMENT OF SUBSTITUTE GOODS OR SERVICES; LOSS OF USE, DATA, OR PROFITS; OR BUSINESS INTERRUPTION) HOWEVER CAUSED AND ON ANY THEORY OF LIABILITY, WHETHER IN CONTRACT, STRICT LIABILITY, OR TORT (INCLUDING NEGLIGENCE OR OTHERWISE) ARISING IN ANY WAY OUT OF THE USE OF THIS SOFTWARE, EVEN IF ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGE.&lt;br/&gt;
    </string>
    <string name="about_title">About %s %s</string>
    <string name="rand">Randomize</string>
    <string name="help">
        How to use this program.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;
        This is a small app I wrote to play around with some directed graph algorithms.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;
        The main table can be created by adding rows using the ADD button.&lt;br/&gt;
        When you add a row, please fill it with the source and destination nodes.&lt;br/&gt;
        The sort button will sort the table.&lt;br/&gt;
        The RANDOMIZE button will create a random graph on the existing table rows, with the number of nodes being approximately half the number of rows.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;
        Pressing RUN will run the D.B. Johnson algorithm for Finding all the elementary circuits of a directed graph.&lt;br/&gt;
        For more details on this algorithm, please consult the repositories as appearing in the About window&lt;br/&gt;
    </string>
    <string name="help_title">Help</string>
    <string name="nav_help">Help</string>
    <string name="no_rows_title">No rows added yet!</string>
    <string name="no_rows">
        Why don\'t you add some rows first?&lt;br/&gt;
        Let me suggest at least 4.&lt;br/&gt;
        If you don\'t know how to fill the rows, just press the RANDOMIZE button.
    </string>
    <string name="error_title">Error</string>
    <string name="illegal_data">Table data should only contain integers!</string>
    <string name="source">Source</string>
    <string name="destination">Destination</string>
</resources>